http://www.alkermes.com/privacy-policy

Protecting Your Privacy
We urge all users of our websites and other online services that link to or post this Privacy Policy (the “Services”) to read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the policies and practices that we have developed to safeguard personal information, and to better understand our relationships with the third parties who may have access to this information.
By using the Services, you agree to the processing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to our Terms of Use, which governs our relationship with you. Your use of the Services and any information you provide through the Services is at all times subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. For California residents, please review the Alkermes Privacy Notice for California Residents.
1. Information We Collect. We have access to the categories of information regarding you and your visit to the Services that are listed in the sections below. Only some of these categories of information identify you directly, but each category offers some information about your interests and activities that could be used to make inferences about you. Information which permits us to identify you directly or indirectly is considered personal data in the European Union (EU) according to the provisions of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). To the extent we collect and process any personal data that is covered by the EU GDPR, we will do so in accordance with the requirements of the EU GDPR. This will be the case, for example, where you are dealing with Alkermes companies established in the EU such as Alkermes plc or Alkermes Pharma Ireland Limited, both of which are registered in Dublin, Ireland. Where you are dealing with such companies, they will control and be responsible for the collection and processing of your personal data. For further details on our EU
privacy practices and your rights under the EU GDPR where relevant, please click on the following link: EU Privacy Addendum. This Policy refers to personal data also as personally identifying information.
Information That You Voluntarily Provide:
Services Registration. Alkermes has constructed certain Services so that individuals may visit us and review information about the products we offer without registering. If you choose to register to receive information from Alkermes, we will collect “personally identifying information” or “personal data” from you, such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address. Your personal data will be used for the purposes of contacting you. Your personal data will not be used for any purposes other than that outlined in this Privacy Policy. Neither will it be shared with any third parties except those who work directly with us and who are responsible for maintaining and/or processing the data as discussed below. By registering to use Alkermes’ features and services you explicitly consent to the collection and processing of your personal data for the above purpose. You also consent to the access and processing of your personal data by the third parties as discussed in this Privacy Policy.
You have the right to consult your personal data collected and processed by Alkermes. You may request its modification, correction, updating or removal according to the provisions of the applicable laws on data protection in your country. Please also see the “Your Privacy Choices” Section below. By registering you also agree that cookies may be placed on your computer in order to collect information regarding your use of the Services and your preferences as described in the “Cookies” section below.
Other Information You Provide. We and our service providers may collect any other information that you provide when you use the Services, such as when you search for content, sign up to receive communications from Alkermes, or use tools provided on the Services to identify resources that may be of interest to you. In using the Services you may provide us with information on your areas of interest or location. We also collect any information that you provide when you contact us directly, such as with a comment, question, or request. We use this information to provide you with the Services that you have requested and treat the information according to this Privacy Policy.
Information That Is Routinely Collected By Our Services:
IP Address. We record and retain the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer or connected device when you visit the Services.
Cookies. The Services may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies including, but not limited to, pixels and tags, and may place such technologies on your personal computer or any other device you may use to access the Services. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers downloaded on to a device when the user accesses certain websites. Cookies allow a website to recognize a user’s device. Web beacons are small strings of code that the Services may use to deliver small graphic images on a web page or in an email. Web beacons may recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies and the time and date a page is viewed.
2. How We May Use Your Information. We may use the information about your use of the services and information on the Services to monitor user traffic patterns;
analyze what our users prefer so that we can design better services and activities for you; deliver
advertisements that may be of interest to you, including on other sites; and otherwise as described in this Privacy Policy.
Personally Identifying Information. You do not have to register to use most of the information and services available on the Services. If you choose to register, we will use the personally identifying information or personal data you give us to send you an email confirming your registration with the Services. We may also, from time to time, send you emails with special promotions or newsletters with information that we think may be of interest to you, or to otherwise communicate with you or respond to your requests.
Vendors and Suppliers. We may from time to time have relationships with different vendors and suppliers who help us design and maintain our systems and our computer security and respond to email and inquiries from users of the Services, or who otherwise provide services to us in connection with our business operations. We will not authorize our vendors and suppliers to access or use the information that has been collected concerning registered users of the Services for any purpose not related to our business.
Law Enforcement. In certain limited circumstances, we may be called upon by the competent authorities in the EU and the U.S. to release your personally identifying information or personal data in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law, or regulation. We plan to cooperate in responding to such requests, taking appropriate measures to ensure that the requester understands the sensitive nature of the personally identifying information or personal data that they may receive. We also reserve the right to cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting users who violate our rules or engage in behavior that is illegal or harmful to other users of the Services. We may also use your personal data to prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity, to protect and enhance the safety and security of our Services, and to enforce our policies.
Product Reports. If you communicate with us through the Services regarding your experience with any of our products, we may use the information you provide in submitting reports to the U.S. Food and Drug Administration, the competent authorities in the EU, and as otherwise required of us by law.
3. Our Relationship to Third Parties. We may use third parties to provide services and information on the Services and we may provide some co-branded services in partnership with others. We also may use third parties to analyze data collected on the Services. We will not disclose your personally identifying information or personal data to anyone other than our employees and those third parties with whom we have a business relationship. Some of these third parties may be established outside the EU where different data protection rules may apply. If we allow a third party contractor to have access to your personally identifying information or personal data, they will only be permitted to access it or use it for purposes that are consistent with and outlined in this Privacy Policy. We pledge that we will not sell or disclose any personally identifying information or personal data you provide on the Services to an unrelated third party without your express permission, except that we may partner with other companies to provide you with content or services on a joint or “co-branded” basis. At a co-branded site you will see both the Alkermes logo and the logo of the co-branded partner displayed on your screen. To access the services available on a co-branded site you may have to complete an on-line registration form, and this registration information may be shared with our co-branded partners. This Privacy Policy will not apply to co-branded sites. You should read the individual privacy policies of the co-branded sites, as these may differ in some respects from ours. Reading these policies will help you to make an informed decision about whether to provide your information to a given site. Remember, you may always opt-out of sharing your information with a partner site by choosing not to use the service or content provided by the co-branded site.
Other Important Information About Our Relationship With Third Parties:
Links to Other Sites. The Services also feature links to websites that we believe you might find useful and informative. Please be aware, however, that, other than the websites controlled by Alkermes, we do not endorse or recommend these sites’ content or services, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware of and read the privacy policy of each site you visit. Remember, the statements in this Privacy Policy apply solely to information collected by Alkermes through the Services.
Advertisers. We do not permit advertisers to display their advertisements on the Services.
4. Your Privacy Choices. You may elect to receive email updates about information regarding Alkermes, its products, and/or disease states. When you subscribe for email alerts through the Services, you will receive an email to confirm your request. If you decide, at any later time, that you no longer wish to receive these emails you may unsubscribe to our email list by following the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of your email alert.
*Deletion Policy. The information that you provide to us is stored on servers that are operated and maintained by Alkermes and third parties under contract with Alkermes. Users of the Services should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove from our servers each and every record of the information you have provided to Alkermes. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of information about you and personal data may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. Nevertheless, we promise that upon receiving your request, to the extent allowed by law, Alkermes will delete all personally identifying information and personal data stored in the databases Alkermes actively uses for research and daily business activities, or stored in other readily searchable media. In addition, we will use commercially reasonable efforts not to disclose any personally identifying information and personal data stored in a non-erasable format after receiving your request for removal, except as required by law. Please be aware that we may not comply with an individual’s request to amend or remove information that was provided to Alkermes by a healthcare professional through the Services regarding an adverse drug event or reaction.
With the exceptions of any of our websites which are subject to EU privacy laws, including the EU GDPR, we do not currently respond to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide a method to opt out of the collection of personally identifiable information over time and across third-party websites. If we do so in the future, we will describe how we do so in the Privacy Policy. For details on our approach to cookies in respect of EU websites, please click on the following link: EU Privacy Addendum.
5. Our Security Measures. We want your personally identifying information and personal data to remain as secure as reasonably possible.
Data Security. We use security practices to help insure the integrity and privacy of some of the personally identifying information and personal data you provide to us. As an added security precaution, all personally identifying information and personal data is kept physically behind firewalls that meet or exceed industry standards to prevent intruders from gaining access. Although we will make reasonable efforts to protect personally identifying information and personal data from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party could intercept an Internet transmission, or that thieves will find a way to thwart our security systems.
6. Changes in Our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to this page.
If we make any material changes, we will take reasonable steps to notify you (by email or by means of notice on this website) and to obtain any necessary consents required by law. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us at dataprotection@alkermes.com.
You are now leaving Alkermes.com.
Contact Us
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Site Map
Follow Us:
©2020 Alkermes. All Rights Reserved
